

CONTACTS



Dimasdemond@gmail.com



085326723965



Jati Barat V No.352, Banyumanik, Semarang



@dimasmu27

SKILLS

POSTGRESQL JAVA(SPRING)

PHP(LARAVEL) **JQUERY**

JAVASCRIPT BOOTSRAP

SQL SERVER SVN/GIT

React JS, Node JS AJAX/RESTAPI

LANGUAGES

Indonesia

BLOG

http://postingankeren.blogspot.com/ https://emulator4game.blogspot.co m/

DIMAS MAENDRA UTOMO

About Me

I am interested in software development, and have 3 years of experience as a programmer, mainly in Java and JavaScript programming languages. For java programming, I use the spring framework and for javascript programming, I use node js on the backend side and react js on the front end side. On the database side I usually use SQL server and Postgres SQL, here I can create functions, stored procedures, schedules, tables, queries, etc. outside of work I also tried several popular programming languages independently such as PHP with laravel framework or golang.

EXPERIENCE

PROGRAMMER

January 2017 – February 2017

INTERNSHIP IN CENTRAL JAVA PROVINCE FISHERIES – SEMARANG, INDONESIA

Create a data upload archive program using php native

THESIS

March 2018 – August 2018

UDINUS – SEMARANG, INDONESIA

Creating a "Bitcoin Price Prediction with Backpropagation Algorithm" program for novice investors in Indonesia who want to predict when prices will rise and the price will go down using matlab

CISCO: SWITCHING AND ROUTING

March 2018 – August 2018

UDINUS – SEMARANG, INDONESIA

Conduct network training with a certification issued by the Cisco computer network technology vendor as proof of the certificate owner's knowledge and expertise in dealing with computer networks with Cisco products.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

June 2019 – June 2021

PT. MUTIARA SOLUSINDO – JAKARTA, INDONESIA

Responsible: Build application for lottemart HRIS

Technology: Bootstrap, jquery, css, html, javascript, JSP, spring mvc,

HQL, Sql server/Postgresql

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Juni 2021-July 2022

PT. PRO SISTIMATIKA INFORMASI – JAKARTA, INDONESIA

Responsible: Build application for Ministry of Trade of the Republic of Indonesia Technology: Node JS (express, sequelize, toad scheduler, Jspdf), React JS(react

route dom, react hook, leaflet, primeface), postgresql

EDUCATION

TECHNICAL INFORMATION

2014 - 2018

DIAN NUSWANTORO UNIVERSITY SEMARANG

Imam Bonjol Street Number. 207, Pendrikan Kidul, Central Semarang